Lots of vodkas, lots of decisions. But what's the best. How are you, my name is Jeff Klein and I am a vodka connoisseur and bartender here at Beak's Old Florida in St. Pete.
And I'm here to tell you what's the best vodka.
Now that in and of itself is a bit of a loaded question.
For me the best vodka flavor taste if money is no issue would be Chopin vodka.
A beautiful potato vodka from Poland.
But if that's not what you consider the best, then maybe you are thinking what's the best for the price.
To me best for the price is going to be Skyy vodka.
Inexpensive very flavorful, easily accessible.
But if you are thinking what's the best without going too high but I still want to spend some money, great flavor, very important to me, mixes with anything, I'm going to say Belvedere.
Belvedere to me is a great vodka, little on the higher end but very distinct crisp flavor.
And if to you the best vodka is getting no hangover, I'm going to say stick with Absolute.
Absolute and water, guaranteed no hangover the next day.
So my name is Jeff Klein vodka connoisseur, bartender here at Beak's Old Florida and that, those are the best vodkas.